Guide to the Artists Space Collection of Artist Files MSS.506
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Dalcerro, Michael, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 64)
- Dalessandro, David, 2001-2004 (Box 11, Folder 65)
- Daley, Cathy, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 66)
- Dalton, Jennifer, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 67)
- Dancey, Mark, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 71)
- Dangien, J. Bernard, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Daniel, Joerg, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 75)
- Daniels, Ellen, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Daniels, Katherine, 1997-2002 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Dannenberg, Annett, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Danowski, Jasmina, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Daquino, Jason, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Darcy, Heather, 1999-2000 (Box 63, Folder 67)
- Darnell, Christine, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Darroll, Robert, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 84)
- Das, Anjan, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Dasa, Ananta, 2001-2003 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Dasgupta, Priyanka, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Dau, Mila, 1997-2002 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Davidow, Julie, 2003-2005 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Davey, Moyra, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Davies, Adam, 2000-2004 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Davis, Eric, 1993-2005 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Davis, Flora, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Davis, Jeremy Ethan, 1999-2001 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Davis, Leigh, 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Davis, Marietta, 1993-2002 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Davis, R.Scott, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Davis, Thea, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Davis, Turner, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- DaWalt, Ryan, 2001-2004 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Dawn, Kimberly, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Dawson, Dennis, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Day, Greg, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Day, John, 1994-2000 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- De Groot, Gerhard, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- de Jamblinne, Hubert, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- De la Menardiere, Michele, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- de Montmollin, Gabrielle, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- De Oliveira, R. Augusto, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 64)
- de Rosette, Angela, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 71)
- De Soignie, Eduardo, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 87)
- De Swaan, Sylvia, 1996-2001 (Box 12, Folder 81)
- Deane, Angela, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- DeBerardinis, Rosetta, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- DeBethune, Agnes, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- deBethune, Elizabeth, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Decker, Greg, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 68)
- DeClercq, Jesse, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Decourt, Vincent, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- DeFilippo, Christian, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Defrancesco, Leslie, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- DeFrancesco Smith, Kathleen, 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Delguidice, Fred, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Dehart, Brian, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Degennaro, Grace, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Del Re, Fran, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Delanoy, Geoffrey, 1999-2002 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Deleget, Matthew, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Deleplanque, Nana, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Delka McCray, Irene, 2001-2004 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Dell'Orto, Suzanne, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- DeLoria Weinblatt, Lisa, 1997-2005 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Delorme, Patrick, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- DeLura, Mark, 1998-2002 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- DeMartile, Tony, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- Demers, Michael, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Demissy, Ronny, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 95)
- Demmon, Casson, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Demonte, Claudia, 1992-2001 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- DeMott, Mark, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- Demovidova, Anna, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- Demsky, Hilda Green, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- Denes, Amy, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- Depoorter, Ellen, 1998-2002 (Box 12, Folder 65)
- Depp, Tasha, 1987-1992 (Box 12, Folder 66)
- Deramus, Helen, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 67)
- Dermansky, Julie, 1999-2003 (Box 12, Folder 68)
- Deroo, Wijnanda, 1992-2001 (Box 12, Folder 69)
- DeRosa, Chris, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 70)
- Derr, Robert Ladislas, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 72)
- DeSalvio, Theresa, 2000-2004 (Box 12, Folder 74)
- Descarfino, John, 1994-2001 (Box 12, Folder 73)
- Deschambeault, Andrea, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 75)
- DesChene, Wendy, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 19)
- Desilva-Johnson, Lynne, undated (Box 12, Folder 76)
- Desmond, Katherine, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 78)
- DeSpirito, Denise, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 77)
- Desposito, Robyn, 1998-2005 (Box 12, Folder 79)
- Desselle, Debbie, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 80)
- Detiger, Jonny, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 82)
- Detrani, Geoffrey, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 83)
- Devine, Daniel, 1983-1986 (Box 12, Folder 86)
- Dever, Eric, 1991-1995 (Box 12, Folder 84)
- Devine, Moya, 1991-2001 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Devine and Stoa, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 85)
- Devoid, Brandy, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- DeVone, Denise, 1991-2001 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- DeVries, Erika, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Dewey, Pamela, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Diamond, Cathy, 2000-2002 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Diamond, Garrett, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Diamond, Shari, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Dianni-Kaleel, Rita, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Diaz, Alejandro, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Dickhoff, Robert, 2000-2005 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Dickinson, Jessica, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Didato, Baldo, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Dieckmann, Katrin, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Diedrich, Louise, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Diepenbrock, Christa, 2003-2005 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Difarnecio, Eduardo, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Difarnecio, Eduardo, 1991-1994 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- DiFiore, Andrea, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Digby, Lynne, 1993-2002 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- DiGerlando, Vincent, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Diggs, J.Vincent, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Di Leo, Melania, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- DiLillo, Lisa, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- dill-Kocher, Laurie, 1991-2003 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Dilworth, Molly, 2000-2003 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Dimitri, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Dimitriou, Tommy, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Ding, Liu, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Dinkins, Stephanie, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Dipaola, Anthony, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- DiPasquale, David, 2001-2003 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Di Pierro, Susan, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 69)
- DiTaranto, Davide, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Djerejian, Madeline, 1998-2002 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Dmytrenko, Olga, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- do Carmo, Alexandra, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Dobkin, Sarah, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Dobo, Gabriella, 1993-2003 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Dodson, Donna, 2003-2005 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Doeringer, Eric, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Dojny, Matt, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Doks, Vija, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Dolejs, Jakub, 1998-2004 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Dolmatch, Blanche, 1979-2000 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Domeyko, Ivan, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Dominic, Magie, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Donaggio, Franco, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Donaggio, Franco, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Donelson, Linda, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Donsky, Elizabeth, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Dor-Shav, Ethan, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Dorand, Meghan, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 89)
- Doret, Michel, 1999-2001 (Box 13, Folder 50)
- Dorfman, Shayna, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 51)
- Dorn, Charles, 1998-2003 (Box 13, Folder 53)
- Dornberg, Bob, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- Dornbery, Bob, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 54)
- Dorsey, Deborah, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 55)
- Dos Santos, Judite, 1984-2002 (Box 13, Folder 56)
- Doskow, Jade, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 57)
- Doud, Tim, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 70)
- Douglas, Sandra, 2000-2003 (Box 13, Folder 58)
- Downey, William, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 59)
- Downs, Paul Byron, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 60)
- Doyle, Jessica, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 61)
- Dragan, Miruna, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 62)
- Drakopoulos, Angie, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 63)
- Dreher, Damion, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 64)
- Drennen, Craig, 1998-2005 (Box 13, Folder 65)
- Drennen, Craig, 1998-2005 (Box 63, Folder 71)
- Drew, Nancy, 2002-2004 (Box 13, Folder 66)
- Driscoll, Rosalyn, 1993-1999 (Box 13, Folder 68)
- Dron, Alejandro, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 67)
- Drouin, Richard, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 69)
- Drouot, Evelyne, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 70)
- Drozd, Luba, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 71)
- Drum, Sydney, 1994-2001 (Box 13, Folder 72)
- Drumheller, Grant, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 73)
- Dua, Thomas, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 74)
- Duben, Ipek, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 79)
- Dubin, Mindy, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 75)
- DuBose, M, 2001-2003 (Box 13, Folder 76)
- Ducharme, Melanie, 2002-2004 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Ducker, Richard, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Ducret, Stephane, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Duffy, Elizabeth, 2001-2005 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Dufresne, Walter, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Dumas, Amanda, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Dumlao, Maria, 1998-2002 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Dunaway, Suzann, 1992-1996 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Dunda, Jason, 2001-2003 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Dunn, Florian, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- duPont, Andrew, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Durgin, Bill, 1999-2003 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Durkin, Julie, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Durrie, Kyle, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Dushkin, Lydia, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Dusseault, Ruth, 1998-2002 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Dustin, James, 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Dwyer, Danielle, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Dwyer, Diane, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Dwyer, Mary, 1998-2001 (Box 62, Folder 92)
- Dyer, Margaret, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 74)
- Dyer, Megan, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Earthman, Stephen, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- East, Brett, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Easton, Janae, 2003-2005 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Easton, Janae, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Ebrenz, Ines, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Echelman, Janet, 1998-2003 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Eckard, David, 2000-2005 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Eckstein, Ruth, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Economou, Theodora, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Eddleston, David, 2000-2004 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Edelstein, Marcy, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Edge, Allison, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Edinger, Carrie Ida, 2001-2003 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Edlund, Krista, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Edmeades, Deborah, 1996-2001 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Edmonds, Michael, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Edwards, Annette, 1991-2003 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Edwards, Barbara, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Edwards, Beth Yarnelle, 1999-2002 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Edwards, Gregory, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Efanova, Julia, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Egan, Kate, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Egea, Maria, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Egiziano, Michelle, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Eichner, Sara, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 48)
- Eichman, Shawn, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Eichenstein, Rosalind, undated (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Eifert, Frank, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 49)
- Einfinger, Carmen, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- Einstein, Ula, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Eisen-Lester, Julia, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 51)
- Eisenmann, Rick, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- Eklind, Marjorie, 1978-1982 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- El-Khalil, Zena, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- Elam, Christopher, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Elias, Sheila, 1999-2002 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Elias, Sheila, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- Eliav, Oren, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- Elkins, Laura, 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 58)
- Ellenbogen, Robyn, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 59)
- Ellington, Stew, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 93)
- Ellis, Jameson, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- Ellis, Loren, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 61)
- Ellis, Tealia, 2001-2003 (Box 14, Folder 62)
- Ellison, Andrea, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 63)
- Ellison, Robert, 1976-2000 (Box 14, Folder 64)
- Ellmann, Barbara, 1999-2001 (Box 14, Folder 65)
- Elrod, Georgia, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 67)
- Elsayed, Dahlia, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 68)
- Emanuel, Dhanraj, 2001-2004 (Box 14, Folder 69)
- Emery, Heather, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 70)
- Emmart, Dale, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 71)
- Emmons, Amze, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 72)
- Eng-Lahanier, Isabelle, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 73)
- Engelman, Rosalyn, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- English, Donise, 1993-2004 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Enomoto, Koichi, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Enright, Judy, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Enright, Nicky, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Ensminger, Michael, 1992-2001 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Ensslin, Mark, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Enteles, Cara, 1999-2002 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Epes, Maria, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Epstein, Katherine C. H., 2005 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Erickson, William, 1978-2001 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Erikson, James, 2001-2003 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Ernst, Matt, 2001-2003 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Ervin, Keith, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Es, Carol, 2003-2005 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Espenschied, Clyde, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Espeseth, Scott, 2000-2004 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Estevez, Nicolas Dumit, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Estey, Donelle, 2001-2006 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Estey, Richie, 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- E-Team, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Eternity, Max, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Etheredge IV, Lee, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Euclide, Gregory, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Eudy, Michael, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Eustace, Robert, 1985-2001 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Evans, Andrea, 1991-2001 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Evans, Franklin, 2001-2003 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Evans, Steven, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Everett, Deborah, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Eves, Bruce, 1991-2003 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Ewing, Gifford, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Exler, Elizabeth H, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Exposito, Alessandra, 2001-2005 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Eyland, Cliff, 2000-2003 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Ezer, Merav, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Fabian, Joan, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Fabrega, Miky, 2001-2004 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Fache, Carla, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Faherty, John, 1998-2004 (Box 66, Folder 26)
- Faillace, Rachael, 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Faith, Marla, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Falby, Caroline, 2002-2004 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Falk, Marianne, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Fancher, Bethany, 2001-2004 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Farber, Eldar, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 72)
- Farber, Enid, 1998-2002 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Faria, Helvio, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Farrell, Sara, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- Farrin, Laurel, 2002-2004 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- Fassett, Roslyn, 2001-2004 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- Faste, Haakon, 1996-2001 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- Faught, Josh, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- Faulkner, Felicity, 2002-2004 (Box 62, Folder 94)
- Fawundu-Buford, Delphine, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- Fayer, Laura, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 53)
- Fayerman, Faye, 1986-2002 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Feaster, Richard, 1998-2000 (Box 63, Folder 73)
- Febland, David, 1994-1996 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Feder, Elliot, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 56)
- Fee, Mariah, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 57)
- Fehrenbacher, Jill, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 58)
- Feigenbaum, Harriet, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 59)
- Feinstein, Emily, 1993-2001 (Box 15, Folder 60)
- Feld, Jeff, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 81)
- Feld, Robin, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 61)
- Feldschuh, Jonathan, 1991-1999 (Box 15, Folder 62)
- Felice, Rosemary, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 63)
- Felien, Clea, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 64)
- Felino, Joao, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 65)
- Fellermann, Stephen, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 67)
- Fellerson, Lisa, 1993-2001 (Box 15, Folder 66)
- Fellner, Gene, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 68)
- felsot, shannon, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 69)
- Fenker, Kate, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 70)
- Fennell, Christopher, 1994-1999 (Box 15, Folder 71)
- Ferber, Chad, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 74)
- Ferebee, Brandon, 1999-2004 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Ferebee, Chris, 2000-2003 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Ferguson, Edy, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Ferguson, Elise, 1994-2002 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Ferguson, Laura, 1998-2004 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Ferguson, Laura, 1988-2004 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Ferguson, Ray, 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- FERGUSON, RENEE, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Ferguson, Sarah, 2002-2004 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Ferguson, Scott, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Ferraris, Carlo, 1993-1996 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Ferrero, Carl, 2001-2003 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Ferreyra, Ivana, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Ferro, John, 1988-2003 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Ferro, John, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Ferry, Joshua, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Fett, Richard, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 75)
- Feuer, Ejlat, 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Fichter, Celeste, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Field, Jonathan, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Field, Lori, 1996-2000 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Fields, Cathy, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Fields, John, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Fields, Suzanna, 2001-2003 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Fike, Jim, 2001-2003 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Filin, Oleg, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Filippone, Basil, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Fincke, Shannon, 1998-2001 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Fine, Joan, 1990-2002 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Finkbeiner, Amy, 2003-2005 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Finke, Brian, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Finkelstein, Henry, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Finkelstein, Laura, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Finlay, Alastair, 1995-2001 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Finley, C., 2001-2003 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Fintz, Jeanette, 1999-2002 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Finzi, Eric, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Fiore, Rosemarie, 1999-2001 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Firestein, Cecily, 1990-2001 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Fisch, Nora, 1991-1996 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Fischer, Glenn, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Fischer, Melanie, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Fisher, Jon, 1996-1999 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Fisher, Linda Jean, 1995-2002 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Fisher, Michael, 1995-2001 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Fisher, Robert, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- Fisher, Stacy, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 46)
- Fiskus, Geraldine, 1996-2003 (Box 16, Folder 47)
- Fitzgerald, Karen, 1990-1998 (Box 16, Folder 48)
- FitzGerald, Taryn, 2002-2005 (Box 16, Folder 49)
- Fitzpatrick, Jason, 1997-2001 (Box 16, Folder 50)
- Fitzsimmons, Joan, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 51)
- Flanagan, Stephen, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 52)
- Fledderman, Gregg, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 54)
- Fleischhauer, Jo Ann, 1990-1993 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Fleisher, Fred, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 55)
- Fleming, Elizabeth, 1999-2003 (Box 16, Folder 56)
- Fleming, Melissa, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 57)
- Flewharty, Candice, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 58)
- Fliesler, Alan, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 59)
- Flood, Melanie, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 61)
- Florence, Tricia, 1999-2002 (Box 16, Folder 62)
- Flores, Gilbert, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 59)
- Floru, Jean-Paul, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 76)
- Floyd, Ayanna Nicole, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 63)
- Flunker, Barb, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 64)
- Flynn, Kathleen, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 65)
- Fonseca de Lacerda, Jander, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 60)
- Foil, Suzanne, 1998-2001 (Box 16, Folder 66)
- Fontaine, Viva, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Foont, Ronnie, 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Foo, Roy, 2002-2004 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Foos, Jean, 1999-2001 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Ford, Nancy, 1997-1999 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Forman, Alex, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Formica, Jennifer, 1998-2001 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Forrest, Margaret, 2000-2002 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Forster, Catherine M., 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Forster, Frances, 1993-2001 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Foretich, Chantel, 1997-2004 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Fortunato, Paul, 1997-2005 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Foster, Fredericka, 1997-2001 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Foster, Gail, 2002-2004 (Box 66, Folder 22)
- Foster, Giraud, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Foster-Leonhard, Linda, 1996-2002 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Foresi, Carol, 1991-2003 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Fountain, Jimmy, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Fournier, Nicole, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Fowler, Adam, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Fox, Marcus, 1991-2002 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Fox, Richard, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Fraga, Carla, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Francis, Donna, 1990-2005 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Frangouli, Nayia, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Frank, Damon, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Frank, Jason, 1998-2004 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Frankenthal, Danielle, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- A Fractal Groove, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Frare, Laura, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Fraser, Amy, 2001-2004 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Frazier, Sandy, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Franklin, Lucy, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Freder, Gudrun, 1994-2005 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Frederick, Christopher, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Freedman, Deborah, 1990-1997 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Freedman, Marcy, 1990-2001 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Freeman, Jane, 1992-1996 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- Freeman, Joanne, 1989-2002 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Freidenrich, Tyler, 1988-2002 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- Federico, Paola, 1990-2002 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Frelin, Adam, 2000-2002 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Freitag, Roswitha, 1989-1995 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- Friedland, Leni, 1986-2002 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- Friedman, Lynne, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 44)
- Friedman, Sally, 1993-2002 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- Friedman, Barbara, 1989-1999 (Box 17, Folder 46)
- Friend Gay, Dixie, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 47)
- Froehlich, Nicolai, 1998-2006 (Box 17, Folder 48)
- Fromme, Julie, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 49)
- Fry, Leslie, 1987-2004 (Box 17, Folder 50)
- Frye, David, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 51)
- Fuentes Walker, Gina, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 52)
- Fueroghne, Dean, 1993-2004 (Box 17, Folder 53)
- Fuerst, Shirley, 1987-2001 (Box 17, Folder 54)
- Fujimura, Kimiko, 1993-2005 (Box 17, Folder 55)
- Fujioka, Yasuko, 2002-2005 (Box 66, Folder 30)
- Fukumoto, Takuya, 1989-2002 (Box 17, Folder 56)
- Fuller, Emily, 1996-1997 (Box 63, Folder 77)
- Furman, James, 1989-1996 (Box 17, Folder 57)
- Furunishi, Noriko, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 58)
- Furusawa, Shinji, 1998-2000 (Box 17, Folder 59)
- G., Donna, 1990-2002 (Box 17, Folder 60)
- G, M, 2001-2004 (Box 17, Folder 61)
- Gabel, Paul, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 62)
- Gad, Simone, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 63)
- Gagnon, Sylvio, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Galiana, Pauline, 1988-2004 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Galinsky, Norman, 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Galloway, Valerie, 1994-1998 (Box 63, Folder 78)
- Gamache, Keith R., 1998 (Box 63, Folder 79)
- Gamble, Julie, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Gamble, Sarah, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Gan, Elaine, 1999-2003 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Ganesh, Chitra, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Ganjian, Linda, 1994-2003 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Gant, Anne, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Gantman, Martin, 2001-2004 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Ganz, Beth, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Garaigorta, Charo, 1990-1998 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Garand, Brenda, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Garbaczewski, Jacek, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Garces, Ana Maria, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Garcia, Bonnie, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Garcia Colvin, Laurel, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Gardiner, Anne, 1995-1998 (Box 63, Folder 80)
- Gardiner, Ginnie, 1990-1996 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Gardner, Susan, 1986-1991 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Garet, Richard, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Garfinkel, Jay, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Gargano, Crescenzo, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Garner, Grig, 1992-2002 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Gartenberg, Erwin, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Garufi, Auguste, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Garwood, Deborah, 1990-2001 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Gasbarro, Frank, 1994-2002 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Gaskill, James, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Gaslow, Pam, 1990-2002 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Gaudreau, Robert, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Gauld, John, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Gauthier, Tina, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Gauvin, Pierre, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Gavarini, Jehanne-Marie, 1991-2002 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Gavin, Christine, 1998-2003 (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Gayer, Tamara, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Gaz, Stan, 2001-2005 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- Gear, Emily, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 38)
- Gedeon, Christine, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- Geerinck, Manuel, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 40)
- Geffner, Greg, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- Gehring, Matthew, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 42)
- Gekiere, Madeleine, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 58)
- Gennaro, Irene, 1987-2002 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- Gennett, Brian, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- Georg, Christy, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 45)
- George, Stephen, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 46)
- Gera, Russell, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 47)